<contentList>
  <content contentuid="hb2cc69a2gaebbg4509g90adgbaf65e403db2" version="1">Magus</content>
  <content contentuid="h8235e249gbc09g4191g9bf9g5ff981ab5581" version="1">As the practitioners of Magecraft from another world, Magi race towards the past– executing what is theoretically possible with science through supernatural means in a bid to reach the “truth.”</content>
  <content contentuid="h1bcbdffbgde7dg49a7g8dfegbf217d7df689" version="1">Magical Energy</content>
  <content contentuid="h507b2239g004ag441cgbac6g131ac76e4c94" version="1">The energy that comes about as the refinement of the planet’s Mana or one’s Od by their Magic Circuits. Needed to fuel Magecraft.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfce69fddga493g4c5ag8f29ged5daf0e1c54" version="1">Sword</content>
  <content contentuid="h6905418dg027fg424dgb80bgadbd7f82da7e" version="1">As a result of having the Noble Phantasm Avalon inserted into you in your childhood, both your Origin and Alignment are Sword. Having recently survived the 5th Holy Grail War, you seek to make your dream a reality even in this alternate world.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcd2cdd21gdfb8g4d2egaeeag7fb7986265fd" version="1">Elemental Unalignment</content>
  <content contentuid="ha2507199gdb48g4bf6gb3f5g1291ca26000f" version="1">As a result of your Origin and Element, your precision with the Five Great Elements is limited. You suffer a -2 penalty to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellDifficultyClass"&gt;Spell Save DC&lt;/LSTag&gt; and spell &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;attack rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0ba02a42gf0e4g4495g868eg7dc7ffbdd2a8" version="1">Reinforcement: Body</content>
  <content contentuid="h31ffd21fg11eeg464fg9f8agba35a67277cb" version="1">You use Reinforcement Magecraft to bolster your body, increasing the damage of Unarmed Attacks by [1], hit point maximum by 10%, and max movement per turn by 10%.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfec1d6b0ga7f2g4c44gb36agf6f78a928803" version="1">Your body has been reinforced. The damage of Unarmed Attacks is increased by [1], hit point maximum is increased by 10%, and max movement per turn is increased by 10%.</content>
</contentList>